[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
The Black Bull drug has effects similar to a date rape drug.
After a while,
it triggers an uncontrollable, intense sexual arousal.
Are you okay?
- Should we head back? - I'm not going back.
Mungkorn.
You're not usually like this.
Mung...
If you want me to get even wilder,
I'll give you exactly what you want.
You can just fall asleep if you want.
I'll look after you.
Let me take it off, then.
Hey.
Maybe we should make it real.
I can't hold back anymore.
We have to do it right now.
We can't do that, not right now.
You're under the influence.
If not now, then when?
Dammit.
You're up, honey?
I brought you some rice porridge.
Eat something light. It might help you feel better.
Anyway...
you were pretty...
naughty last night.
Did we become one last night?
So you're my first?
I was more than happy to be.
I'll go take a shower and go to work.
Wait...
- Hey, don't you want the porridge? - I'm good.
(Yin as Theartha)
(War as Mungkorn)
(Shane as Phuwin)
(Boss as Lukplub)
(Krit as Kanin)
(Tang as Nadol)
(Tay as Saming)
- Oh, my God! - Mr. Mungkorn!
- Are you okay? - Are you alright?
Khaopuk, how could you leave that on the floor?
- Look at this. - You're also to blame!
- Should we treat your wounds? - I'm fine.
- Does it hurt anywhere? - You really...
It was an accident.
- I'm so sorry. - Goodness!
Hey, what's going on?
What's with all the noise?
- Mr. Mungkorn fell down the stairs. - Mr. Mungkorn fell down the stairs.
What? Mungkorn fell down the stairs?
Mungkorn!
Seriously?
Just sit still for a second.
Let me check you over.
Your leg...
Does this knee hurt?
I'm okay.
Are you sure?
Is it your elbow?
It's fine.
Why is it all red here?
Did you land on your face?
- I'm fine. - Wait...
- I'm heading to work now. - Hey, wait!
We should sit down and check you first.
- Let's go to the couch. - No, I'm okay.
I'm fine. I'm going to work now.
Let me check you properly.
I'm heading off to work.
Probably had wobbly legs from last night or something.
I actually caught a glimpse of that NC scene last night.
It made me want to lose my virginity again.
You've actually lost it?
Yeah.
Hey, stop. Don't tease him.
You're making him feel awkward.
You're going to get our pay docked.
Stop messing around.
Well, you started it.
How was last night?
I heard things got pretty wild.
I was all flustered.
Does the Black Bull drug make you feel flustered, too?
No.
I mean, it just kicked in like it was supposed to,
but I'm feeling much better now.
Inspector Thear must have helped you a lot, right?
He's helped me more than he should've.
How so?
Do you want to talk about it?
I'm curious to know.
Sh*t, sh*t...
- Hey, Mungkorn. - Oh, sh*t...
Calm down.
You can tell me anything.
Just take it easy.
Well...
Can I ask you for some advice, Captain Nadol?
It's about a friend of mine.
His name is Ling Lom.
Last night, he went out drinking and got wasted.
While he was drunk,
he got a little worked up.
The thing is, he isn't sure...
if he let the person he likes
give him a protein shake...
You and your friend drink protein shakes, too?
Whoa.
No wonder you're so ripped.
That's not it.
Oh...
I wasn't talking about the protein shakes.
You'd move your hand up and down to...
Make a milkshake?
Count some coins?
No.
Knocking on a door?
Wait...
Okay, stop right there.
Okay, I get it.
I get it now, Mungkorn.
Alright, I get it now.
And then what?
Well...
Ling Lom...
is not sure if any protein shaking happened last night.
But one thing's for sure...
They definitely kissed.
And are you...
No, Ling Lom.
Right, Ling Lom.
What is he worried about?
About losing his virginity?
Was it your first time?
Yes.
I mean, it was Ling Lom's first time.
Okay.
I think what Ling Lom is worried about
is that he's scared.
Scared of what?
That he didn't leave a good impression
or that it might change the way they see him.
I think everyone feels this way.
We expect our first time to be perfect...
even though we have zero experience.
Tell him not to worry.
I'm sure Ling Lom's partner
gets him completely.
And I have one more piece of advice.
If something is weighing on his mind,
he should just be honest about it.
Got it, Ling Lom?
I'm Mungkorn,
and I'll make sure I let Ling Lom know.
- Great. - Sure.
I'm going back to work.
That was really great advice, Captain.
- Oh, it's nothing. - I'll go tell him.
I'm sure he'll feel much better.
Well, Ling Lom... Oh!
- It's Mungkorn! - Exactly.
Your shirt is inside out.
Oh...
Thanks.
Sure.
You should've just told me a little sooner.
Seriously?
Let me help.
- Don't forget to tell Ling Lom. - I won't.
Hey.
You're avoiding me, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
I'm just organizing these documents.
This room is such a mess.
Let's talk later. I'm busy.
Listen, about last night...
I'm so sorry, Inspector.
I didn't mean to. I completely lost control of myself.
I'm really sorry for acting so shamelessly.
And another thing...
I'm sorry for crossing the line.
Hey, listen.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I understand that it was all because of the drug.
If it hadn't been for that,
we probably would've reached our destination.
I mean, you were being that naughty.
I wouldn't have let you go.
I must have done all sorts of creepy things.
Not really.
I think when you're high,
you're actually cute.
You don't find me disgusting, do you?
Hey.
I was flustered, too, to be honest.
You think you're the only one who felt that way?
Someone like you?
Flustered because of me?
Do you believe me now?
I do.
♪That level of cuteness is against the law♪
But right now...
the drug has already worn off.
♪Stirring up my feelings right from the start,♪
♪The fine you'll pay is your whole heart♪
♪You take the blame, I'll take the love part♪
What the hell are you guys doing?
Open wide, Inspector.
Let me check your molar.
Okay, you're not a member of the Black Bull gang.
- Lucky me. - Yeah, you're lucky.
You, too.
Open your mouth.
Open wide.
Nothing suspicious.
You're in the clear, Captain.
We can't trust anyone anymore, buddy.
(My body is 60% made of water if you're thirsty.)
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm itchy.
I'm itching all over.
Want me to help you?
It's okay.
I'm fine now.
Whoa.
Your nipples, too?
Has the drug not worn off yet?
It has.
I don't feel anything now.
How hot do you have to be
to get drugged so someone can score with you?
He's stunning.
Who wouldn't want a piece of him?
Right?
It's not about being hot, Captain.
It's a crime.
Yeah, I know. I was just teasing him.
So, how was it?
Did you seduce anyone last night?
Or did you lose your virginity to someone?
Lose my virginity? No way.
I'm tough.
I managed to fight off the drug.
It couldn't do anything to me.
Sh*t, an electric shock!
Mungkorn!
Where? Let me see.
Here?
How's your back?
- Did it hit your back? - My back is fine.
It hit right here.
Better put some balm on it.
Let me help.
Where? Here?
Right here.
- That was too hard. - Just bear with it.
It's nowhere near your heart.
Hang in there.
Okay, hang in there.
Good job.
If you're not okay, you can do it yourself next time.
Thanks.
What did you do today to have such terrible luck?
Tell me about it, Captain.
Bad luck since the morning.
Mungkorn,
you have North's contact info, right?
Yes, he gave me his business card.
My name is North.
I work as a host.
But with your looks, you could definitely do it, too.
It's not really my thing.
No problem.
But if you ever change your mind...
Here's my card.
Something about that guy doesn't sit right with me.
He might be working for the Black Bull gang.
But he told me he works as a host.
He even asked me to work with him.
It's quite possible.
The big shots...
often throw parties to distribute drugs.
Why don't you give him a call?
Why do I have to do that?
We're going undercover as hosts.
(North)
(Hello?)
Hello, North.
(Who's this?)
It's Mungkorn,
the guy you met at the bathhouse.
You said I was petite,
cute,
and easy to pick up.
Don't you remember?
(Ah, it's little Mungkorn. What's up?)
I'm just calling you to...
You know, you asked me to be a host.
I'm actually interested now.
(Really?)
(I happen to be looking for someone right now.)
Really? I could use the money,
but the actual reason is...
I really want to see you
because you...
are exactly my type.
(Oh, stop it!)
(Sure thing.)
(We have a VVVIP party coming up.)
(I'll send you the details.)
(I can't wait to see you.)
I'm so happy.
I really want to see you.
See you.
You're actually something else.
I had no idea you were such a flirt.
That's an understatement.
He's got a lot more game than you think.
I just learned it from TikTok.
I think one of these VIPs
might be one of the Black Bull gang's higher-ups.
So we have to do whatever it takes
to get those higher-ups to pick us.
So that means...
we have to go undercover as hosts.
None of us know how to do that, though.
I know someone...
who could train us.
Welcome, everyone, to...
Host Training...
(Host Training 101) 101.
With over 30 years of experience in host bars,
I'm here to teach you all about being a host
and how to land a client.
(Black Bull Agent Party)
You look like an anime character.
We had to change up our looks, didn't we?
Do you see those guys?
They're on our most-wanted list.
We need to find enough evidence to take them down.
Understood.
Tonight, I'm going all out
for the sake of our mission.
Let's do this.
Let's start with the first rule.
It's all about eye contact.
(1. Eye Contact)
Imagine...
the person in front of you is a client.
You should be thinking, "I'm handsome,"
or, "Pick me."
Are you sleepy, Captain?
No.
Seductive.
Hello.
What's your name?
Use your eyes to charm them.
Look into their eyes.
You'll love my service.
Oh...
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Isn't that a bit much already?
You're going to be picked all night long.
Hey, we're here to work.
You can't be getting jealous of me.
Come on, I'm all yours anyway.
Let's move on to the second rule,
and that is...
(2. The Smile) the smile, of course.
That's it!
Look, look at him.
Just like this smile.
This is exactly how a good host smiles.
Now, you give it a try.
No way. That's a no.
Both your eyes and your smile.
You're literally shaking.
Now, you two.
Start with the eye contact.
Now give a gentle, slight smirk.
Hey...
Are you guys for real?
I just did what you told us to.
Wanna come with me?
I asked if you wanna come with me.
No, thanks.
No? Come on.
Hey, North.
What's up, Mungkorn?
I thought you weren't going to show up.
How could I not?
We barely talked last time.
This is my husband.
His name is...
I'm Hunglay.
Glad to see you again.
Let's move on to the third rule.
This is the most important one
because this...
is how we'll infiltrate the Black Bull gang.
It's all about the touch.
(3. Touch)
Sorry for being too serious last time.
Let's start the practice session.
Look.
Flash a smile.
Correct.
Closer.
Make the client's heart race.
- Does it have to be this close? - "Hello."
- "Hi." - Excuse me.
- I think this is too close. - Cut!
You did a great job.
Let's move to this couple.
It's finally our turn.
I'm quite a pro at the whole touching thing.
Let's stop it here.
I think I've got the hang of it.
Great!
Good job.
You've earned 100 drinks!
Just like that!
And that is the complete course for Host Training 101.
Now you're all ready to hunt.
Are we all going to be hosts together?
No. It'll just be me and Mungkorn.
What?
Then why the hell did you make me do all this?
I want to try being a host, too.
Being stuck on lookout duty with you isn't exciting at all.
If you want some excitement, you're free to leave.
I'm not stopping you.
Nah.
I don't want to leave you by yourself,
or you'll get lonely.
I won't be lonely.
If anything, I'd actually be relieved.
Give it a rest.
Do you find me annoying?
Or are you afraid that...
you won't be able to resist if we're too close,
so you're shooing me away?
I know my charm is irresistible.
I admire your optimism, Captain.
That red hair of yours...
I like it.
Since you're here with your husband, what am I supposed to do?
It's fine.
We're in an open relationship.
We just go out to have some fun...
and come back to each other.
Got it.
An open relationship sounds nice.
So...
no jealousy tonight, then?
Not at all.
Mungkorn likes a bit of a thrill.
Let's have a toast.
By the way, who's that?
He's been staring at us for a while.
That's Mr. Tiannan,
an ultra-VIP that we have to land.
If anyone manages to close the deal with him, they're set.
He's got plenty of resources to keep the party going.
Make sure you look good.
Hey, one of the guests wants to speak with you.
Two of you, actually.
Let's go, Mungkorn.
Not you, though.
He wants these two.
Open the door.
Open the door!
I said open the damn door!
- Kiss me. - I said open up!
Kiss me.
- What? - I said kiss me.
Whoa!
What the hell are you doing?
Oh, I just felt like the mood was right,
so we just pulled over and got to it right here.
You can't do that.
This is private property,
and they're having a party inside.
I see.
Look, go straight for 2 kilometers and you'll find a hotel.
Go get a room. Now!
My boyfriend likes it outdoors.
But not here.
Go do it somewhere else. Leave now!
Got it.
Hey, nothing to see here!
What are you looking at?
Where are you guys from?
How come I've never seen you before?
I'm from Lampang.
As for my partner...
he's from Mae Hong Son.
You're a couple?
How did you two meet?
We met at a police station.
Well, that day...
I got drug-tested and tested positive,
and I happened to run into him.
Same charge and everything.
I thought it was fate.
Good.
I've got something special for you.
I'm Tiannan.
I'm Hunglay.
My partner is...
Dragon.
You're letting him answer everything?
Can't you talk?
I can.
I'm just feeling a bit shy right now.
Actually, you're exactly my type.
You're my type, too.
Petite.
Easy to pick up.
Tonight...
we're going to have some fun.
What are you going to do to us?
I'm dying with excitement.
You're excited?
How about some treats?
It helps you feel more relaxed.
Treats.
Let's have some, shall we?
Eat up.
I wanted another piece.
Well, he just had some last night.
He's still feeling the buzz.
Okay.
You really love your partner, huh?
Not bad.
I don't know if those two will be too much for you, though.
You know,
in the next 15 minutes,
we're going to take a trip to Fantasyland.
Don't you worry about it.
I mean...
I'm dying to take you with me.
Now that's what I'm talking about.
My radar told me to pick you, and it was right.
Let's get ready to explore Fantasyland with me.
Tell me where you want to go.
I've got a VVIP passport right here.
Whoa, that's firm.
Very firm.
Wine, sir.
Thank you.
You're cute.
Want to sit with me?
No, thank you.
I'm on staff. I have to get back to work.
With your looks,
why don't you work for me?
I'll make sure you get rich.
I'm good, sir.
I'm not ready to be rich yet.
Hey.
With a face like yours,
one cheek pinch could earn you a thousand.
In one night, you'd make a hundred thousand.
Hey!
What are you doing?
No one touches my boyfriend's cheeks.
Wait, he's also taken?
Yeah.
Only I get to touch his cheeks.
We're really sorry.
Phuwin,
you can't be jealous like this. We're on duty.
But he was going to touch your cheek.
I don't like it. I'm jealous.
You're acting suspicious.
You're going to get us caught.
Keep your cool, Phuwin.
Then you'd better stop being so cute
so I won't get jealous.
Come on, get back to work.
Hunglay, are you okay?
I'm fine.
These drugs can't affect me.
I'm ready for the two of you to serve me now.
Let me see...
what special moves you've got.
I'm going to make sure...
you never forget this night.
I promise I've got more moves...
than you'd see in any dance class.
Anyway,
how about we do something to stimulate the mood?
Stimulate?
Stimulate what?
Well, we are going to...
give you a four-hand massage.
That sounds good.
I'm really stiff right now.
If we do it right away,
it won't be exciting.
Let's take our time,
nice and slow.
Does this feel good?
Yeah.
Wow.
Would you mind if I adjusted the frequency?
The frequency is already set.
I need to tune the other side, too.
Tiannan...
What?
I think you should take a shower first.
So the massage will be smooth,
and you'll feel more relaxed.
But I've already showered.
We need to apply massage oil, though.
We'll apply it all over your body.
Oh, okay. Oil...
Got it.
Apply it to every part of me.
Of course.
- Every single part? - Yeah.
I'll walk you to the bathroom.
Make sure you clean yourself thoroughly.
I'll be waiting for you.
Keep a lookout.
There's nothing here.
We need to check that room.
Find anything, Inspector?
I can't find a thing.
Gosh, it only takes five minutes to shower.
Yeah, I am looking right now!
I found it! I think this is it.
- Found it. It's a full list of names. - Let me take a look.
It's a complete list of everyone involved.
Let me see.
It's real.
He's not getting away this time.
We've found the boss.
So...
I'm pretty good, right?
You're amazing, Inspector.
How about a reward?
What kind of reward?
Inspector...
You can't do it here.
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
Why are you messing with my stuff?
What's the problem?
I was just looking for some oil for your massage.
Bullsh*t!
You two are cops, aren't you?
Sh*t. Damn it.
I knew something was off.
I've been all over Chiang Mai,
but I've never seen anyone like you two.
Wait, just take it easy.
The thing is, the two of us...
just came down from the mountains.
Even your accent is wrong.
You trying to play me?
Are you?
You've got some nerve coming into my territory.
You are leaving in body bags.
You little sh*ts!
Sh*t!
You bastard!
You...
I think something's going down inside.
F*ck!
Let me go!
What are you doing?
What the hell?
Let go of me!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Let's go.
You useless bunch of idiots!
F*ck you!
Hey, let's go!
Phuwin, watch out!
Come on!
Hey, we were just about to leave.
Stop with the bullsh*t.
I know you're cops.
We're not.
Watch out, Captain!
Are you hurt?
Blood...
Let go of me!
Get down!
Let me go!
Wait...
Hey,
your eyebrow is bleeding.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
It's nothing.
Mungkorn...
- Are you holding up? - I can't...
Damn, it's freaking hot.
Hang in there, Inspector.
I think the drug is starting to kick in.
You might not be able to handle it.
I'll be fine.
I'll use the effects to my advantage,
but you have to help me stay focused.
Inspector, watch out!
Mungkorn,
why are you such a good dancer?
Inspector, what on earth are you seeing right now?
Kiss me.
It'll help clear my head.
Inspector!
Whoa...
Get it together!
You want it rough?
Inspector!
I'll take care of you, Mungkorn.
I trust you, Inspector.
Can you handle this, Thear?
I certainly can.
Thear!
Inspector!
Hey!
Inspector, stop!
- Stop! Let me go. - Inspector!
Hold on...
I don't think you can do this anymore.
Better let the others handle the rest.
Mungkorn...
Hey,
I'm not holding you back, am I?
Not at all.
You were amazing, Inspector.
Die, you bastards!
Hey...
You should sit down first.
Take it slow.
Just stay with me.
I'm pressing on the wound. Hang in there.
Goddammit, you shot my husband!
You raided my hideout.
How dare you?
You two are a couple, huh?
Then you can die together,
you bastards!
Stop! Goddammit.
Mungkorn!
- Who the hell are you? - Are you okay, Inspector?
What is this?
Stay with me, alright?
Just breathe. In and out.
Are you hurt, Inspector?
I'm fine.
Listen, I'm pressing on the wound.
Mungkorn!
Phuwin, call an ambulance now!
I'll keep the pressure on.
- Hey, round up all the suspects - Stay with me.
- and get an ambulance here immediately! - Are you okay?
Yes, sir.
I'm fine.
Stay with me.
Mungkorn,
you're going to be okay.
Stay awake.
- I'm okay, Inspector. - Listen.
I want some shaved ice.
Shaved ice? Of course.
I'll make sure you get to eat it.
It's my treat.
- Promise? - Excuse me,
friends aren't allowed inside.
I'm not a friend. I'm his husband.
Then please wait outside and fill out the patient's information.
I, Inspector Thear, solemnly swear...
that I will be a good husband to you forever.
I promise to be a good husband
to share in both joy and sorrow
and never leave your side.
Mungkorn's going to be okay.
Even if he is okay,
I'm not letting those bastards get away with this.
They freaking hurt Mungkorn.
I know you're worried about him,
but don't you dare do it alone.
Yeah.
Everyone here is worried about him.
But if you're going, we're going together.
I have removed the bullet.
The patient is now out of danger,
but he'll need some time to recover.
I'll take my leave now.
- Yes! - Yes!
- My bro made it! - My boy's tough as nails.
Keep it down, everyone. We're in a hospital.
Hey.
Mungkorn is safe now.
You can stop looking so grim now.
Do you guys think...
he'd have ended up like this
if I'd been better
or more careful?
Inspector,
stop blaming yourself.
I'm sure Mungkorn already knew...
that being a police officer
comes with its fair share of risks.
In fact,
he might even be happy when he wakes up
and realizes you...
care about him like you're in love with him.
That's true.
Mungkorn must be proud of you, too.
Yeah.
The patient is awake,
but he's still a bit dazed
and confused from the effects of the medication.
I suggest visitors go in one at a time.
Okay, I'll go first.
Right this way.
I can go in now, right?
- Yes. - Yes.
He's still groggy from the anesthesia.
His condition is stable for now.
Okay.
Hey...
What happened to me?
You just had surgery.
You were shot.
I was shot?
Did it hit my heart?
Where is my heart?
Your heart is still there.
Where is it?
Right here.
Your heart is right here.
I'll take my leave now.
Thank you very much.
It really is here.
It's beating so fast.
Who are you?
Why are you so handsome?
My name is Thear.
Inspector Thear.
- Thear... - Do you remember me?
I think I've seen you before.
Really?
Where did you see me?
In my sleep...
I dream about you all the time.
Does that mean I'm...
so handsome that you dream about me?
Oh...
But I think...
I like you.
I like you, too.
When I dream,
I only dream about you, Mungkorn.
Mungkorn?
Is my name Mungkorn?
Yeah.
Your name is Mungkorn,
and you are the love of my life.
The love of your life?
Does that mean...
I'm your love, Inspector Thear?
♪That level of cuteness is against the law♪
♪I must be under your spell, can I blame you at all?♪
♪You're guilty of messing with my heart,♪
♪Stirring up my feelings right from the start,♪
♪The fine you'll pay is your whole heart♪
♪You take the blame, I'll take the love part♪
- From this day forward, - From this day forward...
may there be no more hardship or harm in our lives.
And may we live happily for many years to come.
Ever since we got married,
my luck has gone downhill.
Looks like your bad luck finally wore off.
I'm the one stuck with it now.
♪When you smile♪
♪And you look into my eyes,♪
♪It's too much for this heart to keep inside♪
♪Almost forgot how to breathe,♪
♪How could you do this to me?♪
♪Told you to stop, but you wouldn't agree♪
♪With all the evidence I have found,♪
♪Guess I'll have to take you into custody now♪
♪That level of cuteness is against the law♪
♪I must be under your spell, can I blame you at all?♪
♪You're guilty of messing with my heart,♪
♪Stirring up my feelings right from the start,♪
♪The fine you'll pay is your whole heart♪
♪You take the blame, I'll take the love part♪